avigill@hotmail.ca Portfolio: avigill.ca

Your friendly neighborhood Full Stack Developer

I am a self-motivated team player who has been working in team leader/supervisor roles for many years. I excel at learning new skills, problem-solving and motivating individuals. I am always looking for new challenges, experiences, and learning opportunities.

Skills: Javascript HTML CSS React NodeJS ExpressJS OAuth RESTful API Redux Go

## **Projects**

### emaily

An easy way to send surveys and have responses organized.

JavaScript, Redux, React, HTML, CSS, NodeJS, Sendgrid, Express

#### stock

infinite-bayou-69373.herokuapp.com/ github.com/dootrex/stock

A virtual Stock Trading Platform

Redux, React, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, NodeJS, Express, MongoDB

## Education

Open Source Society University github.com

Mar 2020 to Sep 2020

**Computer Science** 

Javascript: The Advanced Concepts | Udemy udemy.com

Jun 2020 to Jul 2020

Certificate, Computer Science

Full Stack Web Development | Udemy udemy.com

Apr 2020 to May 2020

Certificate, Computer Science

Simon Fraser University

Sep 2013 to Jun 2019

Bachelor's of Science, Physical Geography

# Experience

Gateway Casinos

Apr 2016 to Oct 2019

Poker Supervisor Burnaby, BC

**Gateway Casinos** 

Apr 2014 to Oct 2016

Table Game Dealer Burnaby, BC